songspkmp3.me 2016-05-10

# Privacy Policy - Songspk-mp3.in

Mysongspkmp3.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: http://www.mysongspkmp3.com

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit .

Third Party Cookies

Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

External Links

Mysongspkmp3.com contains links of other sites on the internet. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites we link to. We do make an effort to avoid linking to known ‘adult’ and ‘porn’ sites. Mysongspkmp3.com is a family web site.

Changes To Our Privacy Policy

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site.
